<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
        <title>Digg Top Stories</title>
        <description>Digg - What the Internet is talking about right now</description>
        <link>http://digg.com/</link>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2019 03:00:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2019 03:00:11 +0000</pubDate>
        <ttl>15</ttl>

         
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
        <item>
            <title>The Battle To Separate Safa And Marwa</title>
            <description>It's the rarest form of a rare condition — conjoined twins, fused at the head.</description>
            <link>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/extra/PLNMqvmycN/conjoined-twins</link>
            <guid>http://on.digg.com/30dq0LH</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2019 22:22:52 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
         
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
        <item>
            <title>The Sunniest — And Least Sunny — Cities In The World, Visualized</title>
            <description>If you find yourself craving more sunshine and fewer overcast days, here are the places you should go to.</description>
            <link>http://digg.com/2019/cities-most-sunny-days</link>
            <guid>http://on.digg.com/2keQXPO</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2019 21:15:55 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
         
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
        <item>
            <title>This Is The Worst Kind Of Rubik's Cube</title>
            <description>Humanity deserves whatever is coming for it.</description>
            <link>http://digg.com/video/meat-rubiks</link>
            <guid>http://on.digg.com/2lLUPsh</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2019 17:57:38 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
         
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
        <item>
            <title>Get Unlimited For Just $25/Month At Sprint</title>
            <description>Limited time only! Get Unlimited for just $25/month with Sprint. Simply bring the phone you love or buy a new one outright. No annual contracts. Switch today!</description>
            <link>https://prf.hn/click/camref:1101l4bvV/creativeref:1100l35820</link>
            <guid>http://on.digg.com/2JmTBM3</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2019 11:44:14 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
         
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
        <item>
            <title>Thousands Of Bees Come From Out Of Nowhere To Plague Festival Goers</title>
            <description>Electric Forest Music Festival had to send in experts to extract and smoke out these bees to relocate their hive.</description>
            <link>http://digg.com/video/electric-forest-bees</link>
            <guid>http://on.digg.com/2kd5g7u</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2019 20:17:24 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
         
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
        <item>
            <title>Beyoncé Just Dropped The Music Video For Her 'Lion King' Song 'Spirit' And It's Stunning</title>
            <description>&quot;The concept of the video is to show how God is the painter, and natural beauty in nature needs no art direction.&quot;</description>
            <link>http://digg.com/video/beyonce-spirit</link>
            <guid>http://on.digg.com/2JDLlHu</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2019 02:14:50 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
         
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
        <item>
            <title>Why Did We Wait So Long For The Bicycle?</title>
            <description>The bicycle, as we know it today, was not invented until the late 1800s. Yet it was a simple mechanical invention. It would seem to require no brilliant inventive insight, and certainly no scientific background. Why, then, wasn't it invented much earlier?</description>
            <link>https://rootsofprogress.org/why-did-we-wait-so-long-for-the-bicycle</link>
            <guid>http://on.digg.com/32wwDem</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2019 00:44:20 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
         
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
        <item>
            <title>Alright, We Can Shut Down The Bottle Cap Challenge — This Guy Won</title>
            <description>Can you win a meme? We're not entirely sure, but this guy deserves it.</description>
            <link>http://digg.com/video/bottle-cap-challenge-best</link>
            <guid>http://on.digg.com/2lBWH6A</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2019 18:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
         
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
        <item>
            <title>The Enduring Power Of Protein Powder</title>
            <description>The biggest issue with protein powders is what else might be in them.</description>
            <link>https://elemental.medium.com/pump-you-up-the-enduring-power-of-protein-powder-bcaf31610633</link>
            <guid>http://on.digg.com/2k4e2EL</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2019 23:30:23 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
         
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
        <item>
            <title>The Best Deals During Prime Day That Aren't On Amazon</title>
            <description>Amazon doesn’t have the market cornered on summer sales. These great deals from the likes of Walmart, Moosejaw and other retailers have made us diversify our shopping.</description>
            <link>http://digg.com/2019/picks-amazon-prime-day-guide</link>
            <guid>http://on.digg.com/2WVAVYw</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2019 19:07:46 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
         
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
        <item>
            <title>Man Explores A Mostly Abandoned Soviet Beach Town, Goes Fishing</title>
            <description>Kobuleti, Georgia — which had been a popular vacation destination (in part due to its sex tourism) — sits on the far eastern edge of the Black Sea.</description>
            <link>http://digg.com/video/worst-fishermen-black-sea</link>
            <guid>http://on.digg.com/2JKJdOa</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2019 17:34:29 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
         
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
        <item>
            <title>How North Korea's Leader Gets His Luxury Cars</title>
            <description>High-end Western goods are making their way to North Korea's elite through a complex system of port transfers, secret high-seas shipping and shadowy front companies.</description>
            <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/07/16/world/asia/north-korea-luxury-goods-sanctions.html</link>
            <guid>http://on.digg.com/2LTmClm</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2019 00:44:20 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
         
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
        <item>
            <title>House Votes To Condemn Trump 'Racist Comments', With Only Four Republicans Backing The Measure</title>
            <description>The vote was delayed for hours following GOP complaints that Speaker Pelosi's remarks had violated House rules.</description>
            <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/donald-trump/house-vote-resolution-condemning-trump-s-racist-comments-n1030266</link>
            <guid>http://on.digg.com/2lfdwEq</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2019 00:44:20 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
         
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
        <item>
            <title>Keep Cool This Summer With This Personal Air Conditioner</title>
            <description>Beat the heat with this EvaChill EV-500 Personal Air Conditioner. It's lightweight enough for you to take with you anywhere, while remaining entirely eco-friendly and bio-safe. Get it on sale for 20% off today.</description>
            <link>https://store.digg.com/sales/evachill-ev-500-white?utm_source=digg.com&amp;utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_campaign=evachill-ev-500-white&amp;utm_term=scsf-332489&amp;utm_content=a0x1P000004HZc9&amp;scsonar=1</link>
            <guid>http://on.digg.com/2xMki7p</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2019 11:53:29 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
         
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
        <item>
            <title>Has The Code Been Cracked On Key Switches?</title>
            <description>Input Club thinks it's cracked the code and figured out a way not just to bring the IBM Beam Spring into the modern keyboard era, but also to create a keyboard so customizable that the input the keyboard reports changes depending on how hard you press the key.</description>
            <link>https://gizmodo.com/has-the-code-been-cracked-on-key-switches-1836273727</link>
            <guid>http://on.digg.com/2kdD4kV</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2019 00:44:20 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
         
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
        <item>
            <title>What Happened To Jonathan Taylor Thomas?</title>
            <description>How did the once-ubiquitous star of &quot;Home Improvement&quot; and &quot;The Lion King&quot; fade into oblivion? We investigated.</description>
            <link>https://www.vice.com/en_us/article/8xzy9p/what-happened-to-jonathan-taylor-thomas</link>
            <guid>http://on.digg.com/2keyjaK</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2019 18:02:17 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
         
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
        <item>
            <title>Candide Thovex Shreds Waves Wearing Downhill Skis</title>
            <description>Forgoing a wetsuit and wearing ski gear, to boot.</description>
            <link>http://digg.com/video/candide-thovex-ski-wave</link>
            <guid>http://on.digg.com/2XKOYpg</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2019 23:30:22 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
         
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
        <item>
            <title>The Moment That Made Neil Armstrong's Heart Rate Spike</title>
            <description>Real-time data from the Apollo 11 astronauts, carefully monitored by Mission Control, capture the frenzied maneuvers that put men on the moon.</description>
            <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/science/archive/2019/07/apollo-11-moon-heart-rates/593971/</link>
            <guid>http://on.digg.com/32pBspL</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2019 00:44:20 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
         
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
        <item>
            <title>You Need To Wear Sunscreen On An Airplane</title>
            <description>The fact that our skin is more susceptible to sun damage when we're in the sky is something we're rarely warned about.</description>
            <link>https://lifehacker.com/you-need-to-wear-sunscreen-on-an-airplane-1836371739</link>
            <guid>http://on.digg.com/2LT588D</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2019 23:30:22 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
         
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
        <item>
            <title>Police Officer Arrested After His Bodycam Catches Him Repeatedly Planting Drugs</title>
            <description>120 charges brought as a result of Zachary Wester's arrests were dropped after the investigation discovered his misconduct.</description>
            <link>http://digg.com/video/zachary-wester-arrest</link>
            <guid>http://on.digg.com/2ki7vGC</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2019 22:22:52 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
         
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
        <item>
            <title>Whole 60</title>
            <description>This diet plan requires that you eat whatever you want whenever you want to eat it, and declare yourself beautiful. We’re not going to lie — it's really hard.</description>
            <link>https://longreads.com/2019/07/16/whole-60/</link>
            <guid>http://on.digg.com/2k9CKDS</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2019 00:44:20 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
         
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
        <item>
            <title>What's In This?: Oreos</title>
            <description>All 10 ingredients in these miniature sugar bombs, explained (yep, even soy lecithin.)</description>
            <link>https://melmagazine.com/en-us/story/whats-in-this-oreos</link>
            <guid>http://on.digg.com/2SmknIv</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2019 00:44:20 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
         
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
        <item>
            <title>Get Unlimited For Just $25/Month At Sprint!</title>
            <description>Limited time only! Get Unlimited for just $25/month. Simply bring the phone you love or buy a new one outright. No annual contracts. Switch today!</description>
            <link>https://prf.hn/click/camref:1101l4bvV/creativeref:1100l35820</link>
            <guid>http://on.digg.com/2xMWhNM</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 12:31:54 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
         
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
        <item>
            <title>The Knock-On Effects Of Keeping New Orleans Dry</title>
            <description>Hurricane Barry largely spared New Orleans, but it underscored that climate change brings complex impacts and hard choices.</description>
            <link>https://www.citylab.com/perspective/2019/07/infrastructure-climate-change-impacts-new-orleans-flood-risk/594004/</link>
            <guid>http://on.digg.com/2k8dBcJ</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2019 00:44:20 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
         
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
        <item>
            <title>You've Heard Of Lab-Grown Meat. Now There's Lab-Grown Ice Cream</title>
            <description>Scientists have created a vegan treat that requires absolutely zilch from cows.</description>
            <link>https://www.vox.com/future-perfect/2019/7/15/20694715/vegan-ice-cream-lab-grown-dairy-perfect-day</link>
            <guid>http://on.digg.com/2k23SEN</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2019 00:44:20 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
         
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
        <item>
            <title>Man Hacks Into Scammer's Computer To Reveal How A Tech Support Scam Unfolds In Real Time</title>
            <description>An informative — and infuriating — behind-the-screen look into how a scamming group called &quot;Home IT Master&quot; operates and swindles its victims into paying money.</description>
            <link>http://digg.com/video/tech-support-scam-webcam</link>
            <guid>http://on.digg.com/2kgkoB0</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2019 18:55:32 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
         
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
        <item>
            <title>'Sir' Alert: This One Word Is A Telltale Sign Trump Is Being Dishonest</title>
            <description>I've fact-checked every word Trump has uttered since his inauguration. I can tell you that if this President relays an anecdote in which he has someone referring to him as &quot;sir,&quot; then some major component of the anecdote is very likely to be wrong.</description>
            <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/07/16/politics/sir-trump-telltale-word-false/index.html</link>
            <guid>http://on.digg.com/2lhpyNf</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2019 23:30:22 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
         
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
        <item>
            <title>Palantir Directly Powers Immigration Raids In Workplace</title>
            <description>Palantir Technologies, co-founded by a Trump advisor in Silicon Valley, has created a smart-phone app that helps ICE round up undocumented workers. The number of arrests has shot up.</description>
            <link>https://www.wnyc.org/story/palantir-directly-powers-ice-workplace-raids-emails-show/</link>
            <guid>http://on.digg.com/2kcbTa9</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2019 00:44:20 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
         
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
        <item>
            <title>The Most Popular Baby Boy Names From 1880 To 2019, Visualized</title>
            <description>For the longest time, we were in the age of Johns, but then came Robert and Michael.</description>
            <link>http://digg.com/2019/most-popular-male-names-1880-to-2019</link>
            <guid>http://on.digg.com/2lzeifn</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2019 16:55:13 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
         
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
        <item>
            <title>Zero-Waste Stores Aren't Always Better For The Environment</title>
            <description>Ditching single-use plastic has environmental benefits, but if you really want to shop eco-friendly there are more important things to take into account.</description>
            <link>https://www.wired.co.uk/article/plastic-free-zero-waste-stores</link>
            <guid>http://on.digg.com/2XK1LTT</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2019 23:30:23 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
         
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
        <item>
            <title>New York City Is Still A Disaster For The Disabled</title>
            <description>It's difficult to remember pain when you're not feeling it, and harder still to imagine living with physical limits you don't actually have. But all it takes is a brief stroll to see how badly designed the city is for those who are very young, old, short, heavy, frail, or in any way impaired.</description>
            <link>http://nymag.com/intelligencer/2019/07/new-york-city-is-still-a-disaster-for-the-disabled.html</link>
            <guid>http://on.digg.com/2xZdWC1</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2019 00:44:20 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
         
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
        <item>
            <title>Man Captures From His Window The Horrifying View Of A Power Plant On Fire</title>
            <description>And then he promptly does the right thing and moves the hell out of the house.</description>
            <link>http://digg.com/video/power-plant-fire</link>
            <guid>http://on.digg.com/2kdyFhR</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2019 14:34:39 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
         
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
        <item>
            <title>Win A 256GB iPhone XS, AirPods And An Apple TV 4K</title>
            <description>Want the latest Apple gadgets but don't have a $1500 lying around? Here's your chance</description>
            <link>https://www.dojomojo.com/promo-lookup/317e6a41-b361-4074-a2eb-36d01679c09f</link>
            <guid>http://on.digg.com/2JjWUDJ</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2019 15:23:24 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
         
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
        <item>
            <title>The 'Fast And Furious' Green Eclipse Was Even Faker Than You Thought</title>
            <description>The Hollywood wackiness of Paul Walker's snot green Mitsubishi Eclipse from the first &quot;Fast And Furious&quot; movie goes much deeper than that goofy &quot;Danger To Manifold&quot; display.</description>
            <link>https://jalopnik.com/the-fast-and-furious-green-eclipse-was-even-faker-than-1836384263</link>
            <guid>http://on.digg.com/2LnDRM9</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2019 22:22:52 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
         
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
        <item>
            <title>This Freestyle Soccer Trick Defies Logic</title>
            <description>​Pedro de Oliveira is a world champion soccer freestyler (aka, doing sick tricks), and it's not hard to see why.</description>
            <link>http://digg.com/2019/pedro-de-oliveira-flip-trick</link>
            <guid>http://on.digg.com/2lBlgk5</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2019 15:31:39 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
         
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
        <item>
            <title>There Is Water On The Moon. This Is How We'll Get It</title>
            <description>50 years after the first moon landing, humans are trying to reach the lunar surface again. They'll stay longer if astronauts can find and mine water.</description>
            <link>https://onezero.medium.com/there-is-water-on-the-moon-this-is-how-well-get-it-5933bf9111ed</link>
            <guid>http://on.digg.com/2lJJuZL</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2019 23:30:22 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
         
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
        <item>
            <title>Russia's Permafrost Is Melting And It Could Have A Devastating Global Effect</title>
            <description>An environmental vicious circle is taking hold in Russia and other parts of the Arctic as permafrost — the frozen ground beneath a quarter of the Northern Hemisphere and almost 20% of Earth's landmass — thaws.</description>
            <link>https://www.weforum.org/agenda/2019/07/melting-russian-permafrost-could-speed-up-global-warming-devastating-global-effect/</link>
            <guid>http://on.digg.com/2lJJLff</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2019 22:22:52 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
         
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
        <item>
            <title>The Crowd Goes Wild As Ringo Starr Makes A Surprise Appearance At A Paul McCartney Concert</title>
            <description>We, too, would flip our freaking lids.</description>
            <link>http://digg.com/video/ringo-starr-surprise-appearance</link>
            <guid>http://on.digg.com/2kgla0T</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2019 20:17:24 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
         
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
        <item>
            <title>How The American Work Day Changed In 15 Years</title>
            <description>The American Time Use Survey, an ongoing survey run by the Bureau of Labor Statistics and the Census Bureau, interviews thousands of people every year for a sense of how we spend our hours.</description>
            <link>https://flowingdata.com/2019/07/16/how-the-american-work-day-changed-in-15-years/</link>
            <guid>http://on.digg.com/2lyqlJX</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2019 19:50:40 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
         
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
        <item>
            <title>A Laid-Off Journalist Takes A Job In An Amazon Warehouse</title>
            <description>It's 6:45 am, and I groan — actually groan out loud — as I log in to my scanner and find myself assigned to the fourth floor. Again.</description>
            <link>https://lithub.com/a-laid-off-journalist-takes-a-job-in-an-amazon-warehouse/</link>
            <guid>http://on.digg.com/2jFq5Z2</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2019 22:22:52 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
         
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
        <item>
            <title>This Is The New Fastest F1 Pit Stop Ever. It's Incredible</title>
            <description>The Red Bull Racing team needed less than 2 seconds on Sunday to set a new world record for fastest tire change.</description>
            <link>http://digg.com/video/fastest-pit-stop-f1-red-bull</link>
            <guid>http://on.digg.com/2lynaC0</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2019 14:23:36 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
         
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
        <item>
            <title>The Next Billion-Dollar Startups</title>
            <description>Searching the country for the 25 fast-growing, venture-backed startups most likely to reach $1 billion in value.</description>
            <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/amyfeldman/2019/07/16/next-billion-dollar-startups-2019/#40840f5e1d43</link>
            <guid>http://on.digg.com/2jLGtaD</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2019 17:15:48 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
         
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
        <item>
            <title>Sufjan Stevens And The Curious Case Of The Missing 48 States</title>
            <description>More than 15 years ago, a young indie folk artist set a course to traverse the United States of America through song, accruing acclaim, a fan base, and lots of anticipation along the way. Or did he?</description>
            <link>https://www.theringer.com/music/2019/7/15/20691544/sufjan-stevens-50-states-illinois-michigan-seven-swans-indie-folk-pitchfork</link>
            <guid>http://on.digg.com/2lldWsF</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2019 21:15:55 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
         
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
        <item>
            <title>Here's A Long, Gorgeous Glass Water Slide In China That's Nearly 6,000 Feet Long</title>
            <description>This is how we want all our water slides to be: flowers above our heads, transparent glass underneath.</description>
            <link>http://digg.com/video/china-water-slide</link>
            <guid>http://on.digg.com/2keoN7x</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2019 15:44:56 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
         
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
        <item>
            <title>The Lotus Evija Is A Ludicrously Powerful Electric Hypercar</title>
            <description>In true hypercar fashion, only 130 will be made, and they will each start at £1.5 million ($1.86 million). The price isn't the Evija's only spine-shivering number.</description>
            <link>https://www.theverge.com/2019/7/16/20696638/lotus-evija-hypercar-specs-price-photos</link>
            <guid>http://on.digg.com/2k6OabG</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2019 20:20:30 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
         
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
        <item>
            <title>Inside The Amazon Warehouse Workers' Prime Day Strike</title>
            <description>The company uses a severe efficiency metric called &quot;the rate&quot; to surveil employees' productivity, so workers in Minneapolis walked on Prime Day.</description>
            <link>https://www.theverge.com/2019/7/16/20696154/amazon-prime-day-2019-strike-warehouse-workers-inhumane-conditions-the-rate-productivity</link>
            <guid>http://on.digg.com/2lKHoJ0</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2019 17:33:46 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
         
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
        <item>
            <title>An Engineer On Apollo 11 Explains What Really Caused The Infamous Computer Error</title>
            <description>&quot;It all happened so fast. Not even the programmers who had designed it were sure just what was happening.&quot;</description>
            <link>http://digg.com/video/real-story-apollo-11</link>
            <guid>http://on.digg.com/2lzAKVI</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2019 18:55:32 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
         
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
        <item>
            <title>The Curious Case Of Dust In 'The Lion King'</title>
            <description>How one unassuming special effect challenged animators and made Disney history.</description>
            <link>https://www.polygon.com/2019/7/16/20692330/disney-the-lion-king-special-visual-effects-dust-cg-animation-2d-3d</link>
            <guid>http://on.digg.com/2jFJuci</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2019 18:02:17 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
         
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
        <item>
            <title>Brains Scale Better Than CPUs. So Intel Is Building Brains</title>
            <description>Neuromorphic engineering — building machines that mimic the function of organic brains in hardware as well as software — is becoming more and more prominent.</description>
            <link>https://arstechnica.com/science/2019/07/brains-scale-better-than-cpus-so-intel-is-building-brains/?mbid=synd_digg</link>
            <guid>http://on.digg.com/2kgwcDl</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2019 21:15:55 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
         
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
        <item>
            <title>Robert Downey Jr. Explains Why He Moved Away From Marvel And What's Next</title>
            <description>&quot;I had an incredible 10-year run that was creatively satisfying. It was very, very, very hard work. I dug very deep, but I have not been forced to explore the new frontier of what is my creative and personal life after this.&quot;</description>
            <link>http://digg.com/video/robert-downey-jr-marvel</link>
            <guid>http://on.digg.com/2lLkxNz</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2019 16:55:30 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
         
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
        <item>
            <title>The Hunter And The Bomb</title>
            <description>The story was that a radical man set off a bomb in the desert. But what about everything else that happened?</description>
            <link>https://longreads.com/2019/07/16/bundyville-the-remnant-chapter-two-the-hunter-and-the-bomb/</link>
            <guid>http://on.digg.com/2Ssu8Fj</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2019 21:15:54 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
         
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
        <item>
            <title>How Pornhub Enables Doxing And Harassment</title>
            <description>Pornhub is hosting videos that have been viewed hundreds of millions of times. The women in them say they thought the videos would never reach the internet, and that being doxed has ruined their lives.</description>
            <link>https://www.vice.com/en_us/article/mb8zjn/pornhub-doxing-and-harassment-girls-do-porn-lawsuit</link>
            <guid>http://on.digg.com/2lc65NY</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2019 16:55:13 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
         
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
        <item>
            <title>Listen To The Original Australian Broadcast Of Apollo 11's Launch</title>
            <description>It's a great call, and unlike anything you've ever heard in American documentaries or film reels. Plus, fun fact, narrating this historic moment in world history for Australian radio helped launch the broadcast career of famed Australian presenter Derryn Hinch.</description>
            <link>http://digg.com/video/australia-apollo-11-derryn-hinch</link>
            <guid>http://on.digg.com/2lykDrt</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2019 16:55:13 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
         
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
        <item>
            <title>Snake Bites Man In India. Man Bites It Back. Both Die</title>
            <description>A 60-year-old man died from a snake bite in Gujarat's Mahisagar district but not before he bit back and killed the reptile too, a village official said Monday.</description>
            <link>https://www.news18.com/news/buzz/snake-bites-man-in-gujarat-man-bites-it-back-both-die-2133239.html</link>
            <guid>http://on.digg.com/2PPqHa4</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2019 19:01:27 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
         
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
        <item>
            <title>Canned Cocktails Are Actually, Finally Good</title>
            <description>How today's ready-to-drink cocktail companies are squeezing elaborate cocktail recipes into portable cans.</description>
            <link>https://www.eater.com/drinks/2019/7/16/20691691/cutwater-canned-cocktails-are-finally-good-spirits-mixed-drinks</link>
            <guid>http://on.digg.com/2kd31Bh</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2019 18:02:16 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
         
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
        <item>
            <title>This Historic Map Of 6 Million Syllabi Reveals How College Is Changing</title>
            <description>Researchers at Columbia University spent the past three years collecting course syllabi. Here's what the unprecedented project discovered about the evolution of education.</description>
            <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90376685/this-historic-map-of-6-million-syllabi-reveals-how-college-is-changing</link>
            <guid>http://on.digg.com/2lvUCZQ</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2019 15:31:39 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
         
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
        <item>
            <title>Harbingers Of Paranoia: How The Men In Black Infiltrated The UFO Phenomenon</title>
            <description>Lurking within the mire of modern UFO lore are the Men in Black — black-suited, mysterious agents of uncertain origin who reportedly intimidate witnesses and abductees into silence.</description>
            <link>https://wearethemutants.com/2019/07/16/harbingers-of-paranoia-how-the-men-in-black-infiltrated-the-ufo-phenomenon/</link>
            <guid>http://on.digg.com/2lzvqBI</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2019 20:20:30 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
         
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
        <item>
            <title>Seeing Area 51 Memes Everywhere? The Truth About Them Is Out There*</title>
            <description>A plan to attack Area 51 went viral on Facebook, and a trove of memes soon followed. Some of the posts have irony layered so thick that it could reach the stars.</description>
            <link>http://digg.com/2019/area-51-memes-petition</link>
            <guid>http://on.digg.com/2lnr0hc</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2019 18:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
         
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
        <item>
            <title>All The Latest And Best Longform On The Internet</title>
            <description>Find all the best new longform writing on the internet right here.</description>
            <link>http://digg.com/channel/longreads</link>
            <guid>http://on.digg.com/1NiYbmN</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2016 21:12:22 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
         
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
        <item>
            <title>​How Can I Get My Boss To Stop Dumping His Pee In The Kitchen Sink, And Other Advice Column Questions</title>
            <description>A roundup of the most interesting, thought-provoking and surprising questions that our favorite columnists addressed in recent days.</description>
            <link>http://digg.com/2019/best-advice-columns-gross-boss</link>
            <guid>http://on.digg.com/2SeB6NM</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2019 11:36:11 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
         
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
        <item>
            <title>This Week's Best Memes, Ranked</title>
            <description>It's an internet fight and only the funniest meme will emerge victorious. This week's challengers? Hot Girl Summer, Bagel Boss and more.</description>
            <link>http://digg.com/2019/memes-ranked-bagel-boss-hot-girl-summer-walk-a-mile</link>
            <guid>http://on.digg.com/2xO1mVK</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2019 15:37:17 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
         
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
        <item>
            <title>This Sci-Fi Novel Will Make You Laugh And Cry And Hold Your Breath And Actually Finish A Book This Summer</title>
            <description>This debut sci-fi novel is about a time traveller who gets stuck in the 1990s — for eighteen years.</description>
            <link>http://digg.com/2019/picks-mike-chen-sci-fi</link>
            <guid>http://on.digg.com/2lBWuAB</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2019 20:49:26 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
         
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
        <item>
            <title>Tools To Tame The Wild</title>
            <description>When you spend a lot of time in nature, you're bound to run into problems only a blade can handle. Chop through those roots, hack away at those logs and let's get to work with this hatchet and knife bundle.</description>
            <link>https://www.idevaffiliate.com/31555/idevaffiliate.php?id=609&amp;url=31598&amp;tid1=homepage</link>
            <guid>http://on.digg.com/2Y2yd8d</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2019 11:59:30 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
         
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
        <item>
            <title>This Tripod Is Legitimately The Coolest Thing We've Seen This Week (Yes, A Tripod)</title>
            <description>Peak Design is on its ninth Kickstarter campaign and this one is a doozy.</description>
            <link>http://digg.com/2019/picks-travel-tripod-peak-design</link>
            <guid>http://on.digg.com/2l5JhiY</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2019 19:49:32 +0000</pubDate>
        </item>
        
 
</channel>
</rss>
